gitorious.org 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Gitorious AS (“Gitorious”) opererates several websites including Gitorious.org, Gitorious.com, Gitorious.net. It is Gitorious' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. The following privacy policy apply only to the websites above, for the privacy policies of other Gitorious services please consult the individual privacy policies of those other services.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Gitorious collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Gitorious’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Gitorious' visitors use its website. From time to time, Gitorious may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Gitorious also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and e-mail addresses. Gitorious does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

You hereby agree to the registration and use of information described above.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Gitorious' websites choose to interact with Gitorious in ways that require Gitorious to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Gitorious gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Gitorious.org to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Gitorious – by purchasing additional hosting services, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Gitorious collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Gitorious. Gitorious does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

You hereby agree to the registration and use of information described above.

## Aggregated Statistics

Gitorious may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Gitorious may monitor the most popular repositories on the Gitorious.org site or track usage of Git repositories hosted in Gitorious.org. Gitorious may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Gitorious does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Gitorious discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Gitorious' behalf or to provide services available at Gitorious' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Gitorious' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Gitorious will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Gitorious discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Gitorious believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Gitorious, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Gitorious website and have supplied your email address, Gitorious may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Gitorious and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Gitorious takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## International Transfers

Gitorious products and services may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries around the world. Therefore your personal data may be transferred across international borders outside the country where you use our services, including to countries that have different legal rules on data protection, for example United States of America. In such cases we take appropriate steps to ensure adequate protection for your personal data, for example by using standard agreements approved by relevant authorities and by requiring the use of other appropriate technical and organizational information security measures.

You have the right to inspect what information is registered about you and to correct any errors in such information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Gitorious uses cookies to help Gitorious identify and track visitors, their usage of Gitorious' websites, and their website access preferences. Gitorious visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Gitorious' websites, with the drawback that certain features of Gitorious' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Gitorious may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Gitorious' sole discretion. However, if this Privacy Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, Gitorious will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this policy and on the homepage of the for 30 days. Gitorious encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.

## Data processor

Gitorious AS of Norway is the data processor. The business address of Gitorious AS is:

Gitorious AS  
Nedre slottsgate 13  
0157 NO-OSLO  
NORWAY

* * *

The foundations of this document is based on the same document made available by Wordpress.com under the Creative Commons Sharealike license. This derivative document is licensed under the [Creative Commons Sharealike license](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/).
